(insects trilling)
SAMPSON:
You know, some folks might say
you look
kind of Jewish yourself.
Just shut the fuck up.
One more word out of you,
and I'll blow your head off.
No monkey business.
Uh, Mark Sampson here
for Father Finn.
(indistinct chatter)
(bell clanging)
SAMPSON:
See, I told ya.
Nothing but Jesus here.
Just drive.
(car doors close,
dog barking)
SAMPSON:
Oh, good morning, Father.
Oh, you're just in time
for Mass.
Well, lucky me.
Who's your friend?
Oh, just another child of God.
Welcome, Brother.
Join us.
Hey, Padre,
dominus vobiscum.
Et cum spiritu tuo.
(bell clanging)
Give me the keys.
(dog barking)
(child shouting)
-The body of Christ.
-WOMAN: Amen.
-Amen.
The body of Christ.
I knew it. You're a goddamn Jew,
and you're gonna give me
-every Jew you got hidden here.
-MAN: He's not a Jew.
Who said that?
Stand up and let me see you.
(people murmuring)
Take me instead.
I'm a Jew, he's not.
He's got the number, the tattoo.
He did that in solidarity
with the many murdered millions.
Now come on, take it easy.
-Put the gun down.
-You just back the fuck off.
Don't move, none of you!
I'm a Jew. Take me.
-Sit down. -No, no.
I'm the Jew. Just take me.
I'll take both of you
if you want.
The three of you, in fact.
-I'm a Jew. Take me.
-Hey.
-I'm a Jew.
-You shut up.
-PEOPLE: I'm a Jew. Take me.
-Just
sit the fuck down, all of you!
I'll shoot this fake Jew priest
right now.
FRANK:
No one needs to get hurt.
-All right?
-(woman whimpering)
Just take it easy.
Just put down the gun.
(gunshot,
people whimpering, shrieking)
-Lila.
-(people murmuring, crying)
What the hell was that?
I could have talked him down.
He would have surrendered.
And then what?
Huh? We're becoming careless.
SAMPSON:
Lila, he got
the drop on me in Denver. I...
I fucked up. Sorry.
-(Lila sighs)
-FRANK: Oh, shit.
(people murmuring)
(film projector
whirring, clicking)
♪ Edelweiss ♪
♪ Every morning ♪
♪ You greet ♪
♪ Me ♪
♪ Small and white ♪
♪ Clean and bright ♪
♪ You look happy ♪
♪ To meet ♪
♪ Me ♪
♪ Blossom of snow ♪
♪ May you bloom ♪
♪ And grow ♪
♪ Bloom and grow ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ Edelweiss ♪
♪ Bless my homeland ♪
♪ Forever. ♪
MAN (on radio):
This exhibition game between
the San Francisco Seals and
Sadaharu Oh's Yomiuri Giants.
The Seals will feature
the DiMaggio brothers--
Vince, Dom, and, of course, Joe,
on loan
from the New York Valkyries.
(car and radio shut off)
(intro to slow pop ballad "It's
Over" by Patti LaSalle plays)
♪ It's over, it's over ♪
♪ It's over now ♪
♪ That's how it is ♪
♪ For now it is over... ♪
(door bell rings)
-Help you?
-Morning, ma'am.
W-Would your husband happen
to be home?
Honey, there's someone
at the door?
-Howard Wexler?
-That's right.
Inside.
(woman murmurs, whimpers)
(two gunshots,
Howard grunts)
(woman screams)
-(muffled gunshots)
-WOMAN: Oh.
(thudding)
-♪ Don't try to lie again ♪
-♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
-♪ And promise to be true ♪
-♪ Ooh ♪
-♪ Maybe I will cry again ♪
-♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
-♪ But never over you ♪
-♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ How it is for now it is ♪
-♪ Over. ♪
-♪ Ooh. ♪
(dog barking in distance)
TAGOMI:
Hexagram 23.
Po.
Disintegration.
Splitting apart,
standing apart.
One moving away
from the other.
Something coming to an end.
Me and Joe.
Perhaps.
Or maybe you and me.
Hmm.
You know, I intend
to see him today.
I'll be careful.
(footsteps approaching)
I'm going.
Bridget's getting
the girls ready.
-(distant siren wails)
-Mm.
So what's your schedule
for today?
(horns honking)
Nothing. Uh...
Bridget does the shopping,
the-the housework.
I have... nothing to do.
Why don't you get out the house,
go for a walk?
It would do you some good.
You know, I-I really think
that I want to go back
to see Dr. Ryan.
(Smith sighs)
John...
I need it.
I don't know, Helen.
I promise
I would only talk about Thomas.
(horns honking)
Let me think about it, okay?
NEWSMAN (over radio):
And finally this local news:
The Imperial Energy
Administration has announced
a three-year program
to simultaneously
-(door bells tinkle) -promote
conservation of energy resources
MAN:
More bacon over here.
NEWSMAN:
...and stimulate production
in the Japanese Pacific States.
Minister Mashima assures people
of the American land...
Mr. Cinnadella.
MAN 2:
More coffee.
-How did you...?
-Two can play at this game.
This is not a game.
You following me?
(woman singing in Japanese
over radio)
You knew I was following you.
You're hard to miss.
Tell me something.
Whatever happened
to that film I gave you?
I delivered it to Smith.
Whatever happened to Frank?
I don't know.
He disappeared.
So you're still in touch
with the Resistance?
No. I left that behind.
You still looking
for the Man in the High Castle?
No. No, that was Smith's
obsession, not mine.
Speaking of Smith,
you said he manipulated you.
I'm curious.
What kind of deal
did you have to make?
I gave him my father.
(birds singing,
crow cawing)
Oh, hey, hey.
Hi, Dad.
(laughing):
Well, I missed you, too.
-Hey, Pop.
-Lunch is ready.
I'm starving. Let's go.
-You coming, Pop?
-In a minute, Charlie.
That was a hell of a thing
this morning.
-Oh, you don't think he was
coming for me, do you? -No.
He's just some cheap
bounty hunter.
I've seen enough killing
for one lifetime.
Yeah, I wish
there were another way.
Well, there is. This,
what you're doing here. This.
There's something
I want to show you.
(Frank sighs)
I've been working on this.
Huh?
Well, who's that supposed to be?
The Kempeitai?
No, the fascists in general.
The secret police everywhere.
The-the internalized oppression
of subjugated people
all over the world.
Yeah, well, it looks
like Kido to me.
Ah, any resemblance is...
strictly coincidental.
(Sampson laughs)
Well?
Well, it scares me shitless.
Good. Good, it should.
Now, the sunrise--
it represents hope,
the promise and possibility
of a new day, a new dawn.
But this, this man--
this is the necessary next step,
a reminder of the forces
of darkness arrayed
to prevent that new dawn.
What? You think
people don't already know?
No, I think they've forgotten,
or, you know, they never knew.
They think this world is normal,
and it's not.
You said my, uh... my sunrise
was all over the Pacific States.
Yeah, and the Neutral Zone.
Ah, great.
All right, look,
I made posters.
Take them back with you.
I want you to put them up.
Yeah, there's-there's something
you should know.
Um...
people are-are not
only putting up your art.
They're copying it.
Young people, especially.
They're-they're making it
their own.
FRANK:
Ah, this is fantastic.
-Yeah.
-All the more reason why we...
Look, they're arresting people,
Frank.
-I don't want anyone
to get hurt. -Well, look,
in a way,
it's out of your hands.
Th-These sunrises,
they d... they don't even belong
to you anymore. But this,
this is really gonna get
the Pons' attention.
-And not in a good way.
-You said people need to see
-all this. -Yeah, and-and,
one day, the time will be right.
And when it is, I promise you
that we will wallpaper
these sons of bitches
like nobody's business.
SMITH:
Cause of death?
BERG:
Blunt force trauma.
Was he compromised?
Some animal activity.
But no signs of torture.
Thank you, Doctor.
What exactly did he say
about us?
Uh, that St. Theresa's
hides Jews.
And that rumor has it
there's a whole nest of us up
here in the mountains somewhere.
Ugh. Well, that worries me.
I think most folks think
that Sabra is a folk legend.
Like Sh-Shangri-La, you know?
-Sabra, the Lost Colony
of Semites. -(chuckles)
(chuckles) Not too far
from the truth then, huh?
Well, let's hope
no one misses this bastard
and comes here looking for him.
There.
I'm gonna head into town.
Pick up some supplies,
see if there's any chatter.
What will you do without me,
you up here all alone?
Well, I will study my Torah
and try not to make a fool out
of myself
-at the bar mitzvah.
-(chuckles)
We'll be calling you Rabbi yet.
Reb Sampson, thank you.
I like it.
(insects trilling)
Marks, not yen.
How much?
Twenty-five.
25,000 marks?
Well, it's a big fucking ask.
The trade minister?
Mm-hmm.
Well, my price...
just went up.
Fifty.
Take it or leave it.
(exhales)
Your contact?
Solid gold.
Got a man inside.
Inside the Kempeitai?
How'd you manage that?
(chuckles)
All right.
I need associates, addresses,
business connections--
everything
the Kempeitai has on him.
What makes you think
they got anything on him?
Well, because Chief Inspector
Kido keeps an eye on him.
They have a thick file.
Believe me.
-Domo. Konichiwa.
-Konichiwa.
Suimasen.
Trade Minister, Tagomi-san.
What a wonderful view.
Ah, suimasen.
Arigato.
-My painting.
-(speaks Japanese)
(speaks Japanese)
Uh...
-Some tea?
-Ah.
That is okay.
I'm... I can't stay.
Ah.
I hope I'm not being
too forward, but...
I was wondering if
you'd like to come over
to my house for dinner.
Uh, yes, yes.
Of-of course. Ah.
Wonderful.
I'll cook you
some Okinawan food.
My mother's recipes.
-That would be wonderful.
-(chuckles)
Shall we say Saturday? At 7:00?
Yes. 7:00 is fine.
Well,
see you then.
(doors slide open)
ED:
But John Wayne was married.
So was I, sugar. So was I.
The Duke gave me this
just before he left
to fight with the Rebels.
And... this is the belt buckle
he wore in Stagecoach?
Mm-hmm.
Stagecoach is my favorite Ford.
Yeah, I just...
Feels a wee bit apocryphal.
That means
he doesn't believe you.
O ye of little faith.
He told me to keep it
as a memento
till he came back,
which, of course, he never did.
Oh.
Now, that's a horse
of a different color.
That's me, that's the Duke,
and there's the buckle.
CHILDAN:
Yeah.
Yeah, I can see that.
He was killed in action
at the Battle of Dayton.
Oh. You know that?
Everyone knows that.
I mean, John Wayne.
Wu?
We'll give you five marks
for this and the photo.
That's the only picture
I have of the Duke and me.
Well, buckle's not worth
a pfennig without the photo.
Well, could you see your way
clear to seven?
I-I got my rent to make, and...
and seven marks
might get me through.
-I'll tell you what I'll do...
-ED: 15.
We'll pay her 15.
Fifteen.
That's fair.
Right?
(chuckles softly)
Happy?
(indistinct chatter)
What makes you so sure
this man is still alive?
He's alive.
Zone's a big place.
Locate him,
and I will persuade
the trade minister
to reverse the empire's policy
on black market oil.
(speaks Japanese)
Permission to buy and sell?
(chuckles softly)
You are already trafficking
in stolen petroleum,
doing brisk business.
But we will open the tap...
turn a blind eye...
if you can get me what I want.
(exhales)
(indistinct chatter)
(band playing jazz)
Kido-san.
Is everything okay?
No.
Would you like a little privacy?
Who is he?
Who is who?
The kokujin you were talking to.
The bass player.
He just likes to chat me up
between sets--
that's all.
You were very familiar with him.
Kido-san...
...are you jealous?
You are jealous.
♪ ♪
-(grunting)
-(clacking)
THELMA: So this is part
of the new project? Year Zero?
That's right. Propaganda's
an essential component.
We're correcting
American history here.
Setting the record straight.
Glad to see you've put the best
and brightest on it.
NICOLE:
Cut.
-Cut!
-Okay, cut.
This is the old America.
You are the new America.
I want to see you
full of power, energy.
In fact, get the camera
off the sticks
and move it in closer.
Follow them.
We need to feel
the kinetic potential,
the vitality
of the new American Nazi youth.
Okay, boys, what you're doing
here is important work.
You're erasing the past,
replacing it
with a better world,
a world that is entirely yours.
We ready?
-Okay, back to the start,
please. -Ready.
And action!
-(grunting)
-Now get down low,
underneath them, as they work.
Shoot up.
Make him look heroic.
♪ ♪
JACK:
You have enough gas to get home?
Yeah. I bought some
off this mafioso guy last night.
Cost a fortune.
You can't do, say, uh,
one more night?
I wish.
I got this, you know...
(chuckles)
Ball and chain?
(chuckles) Well,
I wouldn't put it that way,
but, yeah, he's been on my back.
And he's my ride.
Well, take the bus.
I'll pay for the ticket.
I don't know.
Are you scared?
Maybe.
Maybe I'm scared
I'll never go back.
Well, would that be
such a bad thing?
I got my grandpa, Jack.
He's old.
He probably thinks I'm dead.
Furthest thing from the truth.
(chuckles)
Well, look who found
a little courage.
You did that.
I don't know.
I mean, to me,
it seems like you're just...
becoming more yourself.
I, uh... (clears throat)
...hate to be
the bearer of bad news,
but... carpe diem.
It's time to go.
Ball and chain.
(chuckles softly)
(clanging)
(indistinct chatter)
(vehicles approaching)
(brakes hiss, tires screech)
(indistinct shouting, chanting)
Move in.
(metal clanging)
Batons only.
Do not use guns.
Arrest them.
(shouting, screaming)
(grunts, groans)
(groans)
(indistinct shouting continues)
-Get her in here.
-Let's go.
Come on. Let's leave.
Go, go, go, go, go.
-Hey!
-All right, we're going.
-What the hell are you
doing here? -(screams)
Where did you come from?
-(screaming)
-(grunts)
(grunting)
(shouting, screaming)
(screaming)
WOMAN:
No! No!
(indistinct shouting)
♪ ♪
-We have to do something.
-It's too late for him.
-No. You have to...
-Let's go.
(indistinct shouting, screaming,
fire crackling)
That was horrific.
(exhales)
Hey.
There was nothing
that we could have done.
Who would do something like that
to themselves?
Look, people are capable
of anything.
(sighs) Especially when
they're desperate.
Are they?
You know they are.
JULIANA:
I need a drink.
Yeah. (clears throat)
You?
Sure.
-(Joe clears throat)
-(sirens wail in distance)
(liquid pouring)
JULIANA:
(clears throat) I, um...
I'm sorry. There's...
no ice.
-(clears throat)
-Cheers.
What's all this?
Uh, there's a place called, um,
Lackawanna,
in Pennsylvania.
Ring a bell?
Mmm. Should it?
It's somewhere in the Poconos.
You planning on taking
a vacation to the Reich?
(chuckles) Of course not.
Then what's with the map?
Just got interested.
Do you believe in past lives?
Other lives?
Reichsfuhrer Himmler does.
So maybe there's
something to it.
Hey.
Me, uh, no.
Not so much.
Listen...
I have a memory
of a place, this place.
And I'm sure I've been there,
but I haven't.
Not in this life.
JOE:
It's déjà vu.
Everybody has those moments.
I'm sure I've been there
with you.
I wish.
I'm sure I've been here
with you, too.
Many, many times.
Me, too.
I've imagined this moment...
many times.
TAGOMI:
Howard Wexler.
Who is he?
A defector from the Reich.
Like Diels.
Only much more valuable.
A researcher.
I believe it was the same
assassin in both cases.
Wexler was working with
your ministry.
On a project I cannot discuss.
The Nazis are doing their best
to sabotage us.
And they are succeeding.
These street protests...
The street protests are
under control.
The agitators
are suffering for oil.
Kerosene. Gasoline.
Heating oil.
What are you doing about it,
Trade Minister?
Again,
nothing I will discuss with you,
Chief Inspector.
(indistinct conversation
in distance)
Hey.
Did you sleep?
JULIANA:
I had this dream...
I've had it before.
Something's happened.
And the world's turned to ash,
and then I'm in this tunnel.
With you.
(laughs)
What?
Well, I'm happy to be
a part of your nightmare.
We got to get you out of
this place, Juliana.
It's...
I'd have nightmares
living in a place like this.
We could get away from here.
Go on a trip.
Visit-- what was it called?
Lackawanna.
Yeah, the Poconos.
Yeah, but like you said,
it's in the Reich.
I have my connections.
Yeah, I know you do.
I got to go.
(woman singing in German)
(singing continues)
This apartment, it's... amazing.
My father's New York
pied-à-terre.
It's ridiculous, I know.
But I enjoy it.
(laughing): I-I don't think
snooker's my game.
You just need practice.
Come over any time.
In fact, if you really want
to write a column
-about my work...
-Year Zero.
...then perhaps we should meet
on a regular basis.
Well, I want to know
all about it.
How much time do you have?
Wayne's off with a friend
tonight.
Well, in that case...
Mmm.
(singing continues)
JOE: I have the plans,
or the... equations?
At least I think I do.
I'm sorry, sir,
I flunked physics.
HIMMLER (on telephone):
You dealt a real blow
to their efforts to copy
our Nebenwelt project.
JOE:
Thank you, sir.
You have a plan
to deal with the trade minister?
I'm working on it, sir.
HIMMLER:
It was through Tagomi's efforts
that the traitor Wexler
defected.
He knows too much.
I just need a little more time,
sir.
HIMMLER:
Well, you are on the ground.
That is for you to decide when
and where to strike Tagomi.
But don't delay too long.
Yes, Mein Fuhrer.
This is what you were born for,
Josef.
(film projector whirring)
♪ ♪
(siren wailing in distance)
Thomas?
(fire crackling)
♪ ♪
Sir, over here.
He went this way.
Just ahead.
(indistinct conversation,
laughter)
(motor rumbling)
THOMAS:
Father.
(distorted echo)
-Over here.
-(distorted echo)
(screaming in distance)
GIRL:
Mommy! Mommy!
(girl crying)
(children wailing, crying)
Help me.
(crying):
Mommy!
(screaming)
Hello, John.
(shrieks)
Cincinnati's beautiful
in the fall...
(screaming, crying)
...isn't it?
(distorted screaming)
-You can't stop it.
-(screaming)
-John!
-(gasps)
(panting)
♪ ♪
♪ Happy days are here again ♪
♪ The skies above
are clear again ♪
♪ Let us sing a song
of cheer again ♪
♪ Happy days are here again ♪
♪ All together shout it now... ♪
You and I, my friend,
will be spending our days
swimming in yen.
Yeah, about that...
Ed, I'm not budging
on our split.
We already talked about this.
I don't give a damn
about your split.
I'm just saying,
there's no reason why
you and I need
to be attached at the hip.
We're partners.
We made a deal.
-Yeah, but lifelong?
-No, of course not.
I'm not tied to you, you know.
I'm free, free to do whatever
I want, go wherever I want.
-I never said you weren't.
-I got a life, too, you know.
-I never said you didn't!
-All right, fine.
Fine.
(man shouting)
-(engine revs)
-ED: Hey. Look. -MAN: Yeah!
-Hmm?
-(motorcycle engine revving)
CHILDAN:
What do they want?
Geez. What the hell's
that guy's problem?
-I don't know. I don't know.
Keep driving. -Pull over!
-ED: Shit. Get the gun.
-MAN: Pull over!
-What? -Get the fucking gun.
-(loud thudding on bus)
-What, are you, crazy?
-All right, fine, I'll get it.
-No. No, no. Wait. Wait. Are you
out of your mind? -Let go.
-Hey, there are too many
of them. -Childan, stop.
-(tires squealing) -Good God,
watch the road. Just...
-Put the gun down!
-(gunshot)
Shit! (panting)
-(bikers hooting)
-Stop, stop, stop.
BIKER:
Nice shot!
-(man laughs)
-Put the gun down.
Put it down.
(motorcycle revs)
-MAN: You all set?
-MAN 2: Yeah.
(indistinct chatter)
CHILDAN: Careful, sir.
That's an antique.
It's actually a fine example
of Belle Epoque gunsmithing.
-(gunshot)
-(laughter)
Shut up.
That's enough talking
out of you.
What's all this old shit
you're hauling?
Ah, it's all just junk, really.
Just a bunch of stuff
that belonged to my granddad
that we're taking back home.
(birds singing,
insects trilling)
(wind whistling)
(whoops)
That's some expensive-ass junk.
CHILDAN:
Let me explain.
That record book-- it's not
for the items in our bus.
Okay, boys, let's roll.
Go.
-Sir?
-Listen to me.
You can't take our things.
-(groans)
-(man laughs)
Please.
That's everything we got.
Everything you had.
BIKER:
Let's go. Load her up.
You know, a couple resourceful
paddies in the Neutral Zone--
I'm sure you'll land
on your feet again.
MAN:
Yeah, let's go.
(engines starting, revving)
(bikers whoop)
See you around. (laughs)
MAN:
Make 'em walk!
♪ Do, wah-wah, wah,
do, wah-wah, wah ♪
♪ Do, wah-wah-wah-wah-wah,
wah, ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ Do, wah-wah, wah,
do, wah-wah, wah ♪
♪ Do, wah-wah-wah-wah-wah,
wah, ah-ah-ah... ♪
♪ ♪
(bells on door tinkle)
(door closes, bells tinkle)
♪ ♪
(birds singing)
(speaking Japanese)
Konbanwa, Tagomi-san.
Welcome.
(speaking Japanese)
You shouldn't have.
Thank you so much.
-(speaking Japanese)
-(laughs)
(speaks Japanese)
Come on in.
(both speaking Japanese)
MAN (over radio): The incident
took place in Union Square
and was quickly brought
under control.
13 criminals were arrested
and charged
with crimes against the empire.
-Now back to your regular
program. -(knock at door)
(horns honking outside)
-(pop music playing)
-WYATT: Santa Fe?
(sighs)
Um, just a second.
Wyatt.
What are you doing here?
I got your note, and
it said if I was ever
in town to look you up.
So here I am.
Right.
I'm beginning to think
you're not gonna ask me in.
Uh... (laughs)
It-it's late.
Have you got a fella in there?
Is that it?
-No, sir.
-Hey, fella?
-(laughs)
-Come out.
Okay.
You free tomorrow night?
How many days are you here?
Two or three days.
I'm gonna take that as a "yes."
(Juliana sighs)
Go to a payphone,
call this number
and ask for Liam.
-And who's Liam?
-Me.
I'm Liam.
Okay, Liam.
(laughs)
(lively chatter,
guitar playing blues music)
House red.
You got it.
So what's the word?
MAN:
You know this guy?
Have you seen this guy?
(liquid pouring)
-Do you know him?
-MAN: No idea.
(loud, lively chatter)
(Lila sniffles)
You know him?
Nope.
-You sure?
-Yes, sir.
(dog barking in distance)
(gasps)
(speaking Japanese)
You shouldn't have.
Thank you.
(speaks Japanese)
Very beautiful.
I have to say
I was so embarrassed
when I didn't know
you were the trade minister.
It's not required that you know.
Hmm. And I was so impressed
by the view of the bridge
from your office.
It is quite beautiful.
Please.
Hai.
-Let us eat.
-Hai.
Uh...
(laughing)
-Oh.
-(speaks Japanese)
-(speaking Japanese)
-(laughing)
Mmm.
Mmm!
(horns honking)
I thought you were in bed.
Couldn't sleep.
You look tired.
I am tired.
HELEN:
I miss our old life.
Our home.
And I feel it...
slipping away.
I don't want it
to slip away, John.
You understand that,
don't you?
Yeah, I do.
Listen, I... I've been thinking
about what you asked, and...
maybe you should see Dr. Ryan
again, just for a while.
Thank you.
-Hmm.
-Thank you.
(speaking Japanese)
(dog barking in distance)
(dog barking,
insects trilling)
♪ ♪
(clicking)